The Hudson River Environmental Society Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 4. Scientific Studies, 4; 5 linear feet 9 - 13 331 - 497
  - Scientific Studies, Box 9; 4
    - 1974 - White Perch Regional Densities, 335 (Box 9)
    - 1975 - American Shad Catch Summary, 336 (Box 9)
    - 1975 - Atlantic Tomcoo Catch Summary, 337 (Box 9)
    - 1975 - Axial Trawl Comb CPUE Day Only, 338 (Box 9)
    - 1975 - Bay Anchovy Catch Summary, 339 (Box 9)
    - 1975 - Beach Seine CPUE Day Only, 340 (Box 9)
    - 1975 - Clupeid Larvae Catch Summary, 341 (Box 9)
    - 1975 - Fall Shoals Survey, 342 (Box 9)
    - 1975 - White Perch Catch Summary, 343 (Box 9)
    - 1976 - Haul & Gill Study, 344 (Box 9)
    - Age-Specific Variation in Reproductive Effort in Female Hudson River Striped Bass, 345 (Box 9)
    - Aquatic Ecology Studies 1976, pg. 1-100, 346 (Box 9)
    - Aquatic Ecology Studies 1976, pg 101-200, 347 (Box 9)
    - Aquatic Ecology Studies 1976, pg. 201-300, 348 (Box 9)
    - Aquatic Ecology Studies 1976, pg. 301-400, 349 (Box 9)
    - Aquatic Ecology Studies 1976, pg. 401-451, 350 (Box 9)
    - Bay Anchovy Studies, 351 (Box 9)
    - Biological Monitoring Reports, 352 (Box 9)
    - Capital District Hudson River Corridor Study - Presentation Format, 353 (Box 9)
    - Castle Lake Business Plaza SEQR Case Study #1, 354 (Box 9)
    - Catskill Creek - Draft Summary Report, 355 (Box 9)
    - Coastal Zone Management Publications, 1976, 356 (Box 9)
    - Commercial Fisheries for Striped Bass in the Hudson River, 357 (Box 9)
    - Commercial Fisheries for Striped Bass in the Hudson River, 1931-1980, 358 (Box 9)
    - Comparison of Major Flood Items of Striped Bass by Index of Importance, 359 (Box 9)
    - (a) Conservation Journal - On Section 404 of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 360 (Box 9)
    - Contributions to the Biology of Shortnose Sturgeon..., 361 (Box 9)
    - Critical Areas of the Hudson River Estuary, 362 (Box 9)
    - Dam Studies, 363 (Box 9)
    - Data Listing for 1975 Life Stage Duration Studies on Hudson River Striped Bass, 364 (Box 9)
    - Delaware River Basin: Comprehensive Fisheries Management Plan (Pre-Plan 1977), 365 (Box 9)
    - Delaware River Basin: Performance Report, 1978, 366 (Box 9)
    - Delaware River Basin: Proposed Fishery Research Program, 367 (Box 9)
    - Delaware River Basin: Statement of Purpose, 368 (Box 9)
    - Delaware River Basin: Tri-State Fishery Study, 369 (Box 9)
    - Development Opportunity Areas - Urban, 370 (Box 9)
    - Distributions and Movements of the Early Life Stages of Three ALOSA. ..., 371 (Box 9)
    - Dredging Material Research Program, 372 (Box 9)
    - Dutchess County - Regulations Analysis, 373 (Box 9)
    - Dye-Dispersion Study at... Cornwall, 374 (Box 9)
    - Ecosystem Analysis & Predition, 375 (Box 9)
    - (the) Effectiveness of a Barrier Net in the Reduction of White Perch..., 376 (Box 9)
    - Emergency Striped Bass Study, 377 (Box 9)
    - Entrainment Data, 1973, 378 (Box 9)
    - (the) Environmental Impact of Supplying Power to the Con Edison Service Territory: 1975-1990, 379 (Box 9)
    - Environmental Quality of the Wallkill River..., 380 (Box 9)
    - Esopus Creek - Draft Summary, 381 (Box 9)
    - Esopus Creek - Proposal, 382 (Box 9)
  - Scientific Studies, Box 10; 4
    Scientific Studies F-R
    - Feasibility Study and Design Development Striped Bass Fish Hatchery, 383 (Box 10)
    - Feeding Selectivity of Larval Striped Bass..., 384 (Box 10)
    - Fi Factor Calculations, 385 (Box 10)
    - First Annual Progress Report on Fisheries Investigations..., 386 (Box 10)
    - First Annual Progress Report on Fisheries Investigations... (duplicate), 387 (Box 10)
    - Fish Data, 388 (Box 10)
    - Fish Ratio Data, 389 (Box 10)
    - Fish Withdrawal - Con. Ed. Nuclear Power Plant, 390 (Box 10)
    - Fisheries Data Sets, 391 (Box 10)
    - Fishkill Creek - Environmental Quality of the Drainage, 392 (Box 10)
    - Food Habits of the Hudson River Amphipod..., 393 (Box 10)
    - Forests in the Visual Landscape - Resources Assessment, 394 (Box 10)
    - (the) Future of Fisheries Research in the Hudson River, 395 (Box 10)
    - Geology and Mineral Resources of the Lower and Middle Hudson Valley, 396 (Box 10)
    - Heavy Metals in Finfish and Selected Macroinvertebrates..., 397 (Box 10)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Investigations 1965-1968, 398 (Box 10)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Investigations 1965-1968 Appendix, 399 (Box 10)
    - Hudson River PCBs Reassessment Remedial Investigation/Feasibility Study, 400 (Box 10)
    - Hudson River Valley Study, 401 (Box 10)
    - Ichthyoplankton Studies, 1982-1985, 402 (Box 10)
    - Inhouse Bibliography of Publications on the Fisheries of the Hudson River, 403 (Box 10)
    - Initial and Extended Survival of Fish..., 404 (Box 10)
    - Interstate Sanitation Commission Annual Report 1994, 405 (Box 10)
    - Length Frequency Study, 406 (Box 10)
    - Liberty State Park Ecological Study: 1st Quarterly Report, 407 (Box 10)
    - Life History of Atlantic Tomcod..., 408 (Box 10)
    - Lists and Revisions, 409 (Box 10)
    - Lists of Special Scientific Reports..., 410 (Box 10)
    - LMS Fish Population Model vs. Phil Goodyear, 411 (Box 10)
    - Management Recommendations for a Hudson River Atlantic Sturgeon Fishery..., 412 (Box 10)
    - Matrixes, 413 (Box 10)
    - Monitoring of PCBs in Fish Taken from the Hudson River 10/1975 (1), 414 (Box 10)
    - Monitoring of PCBs in Fish Taken from the Hudson River 10/1975 (2), 415 (Box 10)
    - Notification of Changes, Additions, or Deletions to Finalized Data 03/1978, 416 (Box 10)
    - Notification of Changes, Additions, or Deletions to Finalized Data 04/1978, 417 (Box 10)
    - (an) Objective Overview of 316(a) Demonstration Materials for... Power Plants..., 418 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Westchester County 1965, 419 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Columbia County 1966, 420 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Columbia County 1967, 421 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Rockland County 1968, 422 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Ulster County 1969, 423 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Westchester County 1970, 424 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Dutchess County 1971, 425 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Columbia County 1972, 426 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore 1973, 427 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Columbia County 1974, 428 (Box 10)
    - Operating Unit Data - Boats and Shore, Putnam County 1975, 429 (Box 10)
    - Ossining - Biological Work, 430 (Box 10)
    - Patterns of Larval Movement of Striped Bass..., 431 (Box 10)
    - PCB Patterns in Hudson River Fish, 432 (Box 10)
    - Plankton Sampling System, 433 (Box 10)
    - Prattsville Pumped Storage Project: Water Quality Report, 434 (Box 10)
    - Potential Effects of Hudson Power Plants on Survival of Young-of-the-Year Striped Bass, 435 (Box 10)
    - Potential Effects of Hudson Power Plants on Survival of Young-of-the-Year Striped Bass (duplicate), 436 (Box 10)
    - Preliminary Evaluation of the Potential Impact on the Fisheries of the Hudson... by... Cornwall, 437 (Box 10)
    - Quirk, Lawlor, and Matusky Engineers, 438 (Box 10)
    - Ramapo River - Summary Study Report, 439 (Box 10)
    - (the) Rearing of Hudson River Striped Bass at the Edenton National Fish Hatchery 1975, 440 (Box 10)
    - Relationship Between Population Density and Growth for Juvenile Striped Bass in the Hudson River, 441 (Box 10)
    - Relationship Between Temperature and Size of... Bass, 442 (Box 10)
    - Relationship of Temperature to Growth and Abundance of Morone..., 443 (Box 10)
    - Results and Input Conditions of the LMCS Fish Life Cycle Model, 444 (Box 10)
    - Review of Conservation Efforts in Selected Landscapes of the Northeast & Mid-Atlantic States, 445 (Box 10)
    - Rondout Creek - Draft Summary Report, 446 (Box 10)
  - Scientific Studies, Box 11; 4
    Scientific Studies S-Z
    - Salt Front Study, 447 (Box 11)
    - Sanitary Landfill - Project Review, 448 (Box 11)
    - Shad Studies, 449 (Box 11)
    - Striped Bass Scale Analysis, 450 (Box 11)
    - Striped Bass Stock Assessment: Overview and Synthesis of Programs Revised Outline, 451 (Box 11)
    - Striped Bass Study on Danskammer, Roseton, Indian Point, and Bowline, 452 (Box 11)
    - Striped Bass Study & Draft Proposal, 453 (Box 11)
    - Striped Bass Studies, 454 (Box 11)
    - Structure for Viewing Water Resources Management..., 455 (Box 11)
    - Sturgeon Study, 456 (Box 11)
    - Summary of Published Estimates of Exploitation Rates in Fish Populations, 457 (Box 11)
    - (a) Survey of the Inverterbrates from Selected Sites of the Lower Hudson River, 458 (Box 11)
    - Terrestrial Assessment Study - Conclusions, 459 (Box 11)
    - Toxic Surveillance Network, 1982-1983, 460 (Box 11)
    - Toxic Surveillance Network, 1984-1985, 461 (Box 11)
    - Urban Land Analysis, 462 (Box 11)
    - URI Critical Scale Analysis, 463 (Box 11)
    - Various Species and Ecosystem Studies, 464 (Box 11)
    - Various Tables, 465 (Box 11)
    - Water Resource Conflicts in the Hudson River Basin, 466 (Box 11)
    - Water Systems Survey and Data Update, 467 (Box 11)
    - Water Quality Classifications, 468 (Box 11)
    - Water Quality Inventory Report, 1975, 469 (Box 11)
    - White Perch Studies, 470 (Box 11)
  - Scientific Studies, Box 12; 4
    Scientific Studies Large A-Paul Rago ETM
    - Ecological Analysts, Inc. - Entrainment Survival Studies 1978 (1), 471 (Box 12)
    - Ecological Analysts, Inc. - Entrainment Survival Studies 1978 (2), 472 (Box 12)
    - Ecological Analysts, Inc. - Entrainment Survival Studies 1978 (3), 473 (Box 12)
    - Ecological Analysts, Inc. - Entrainment Survival Studies 1978 (4), 474 (Box 12)
    - Land Use for River Basins, 475 (Box 12)
    - Latent Only Thru July 14, 1974 - July 13, 1975, 476 (Box 12)
    - Listing of Batchetm, 477 (Box 12)
    - Map #17 Depth of Bedrock, 478 (Box 12)
    - OBJ ETM Short Version, 479 (Box 12)
    - Rago ETM All Species Dir/Indirect, 480 (Box 12)
    - Paul Rago ETM All Species - Latent Run #1, 481 (Box 12)
    - Paul Rago ETM All Species - Latent (all except run #1), 482 (Box 12)
    - Paul Rago Listings and Example of ETM -- To CRNL, 483 (Box 12)
    - Paul Rago ETM Runs 1-12 Striped Bass - Direct & Indirect (1), 484 (Box 12)
    - Paul Rago ETM Runs 1-12 Striped Bass - Direct & Indirect (2), 485 (Box 12)
    - Paul Rago ETM Runs 1-12 Striped Bass - Latent (1), 486 (Box 12)
    - Paul Rago ETM Runs 1-12 Striped Bass - Latent (2), 487 (Box 12)
    - Paul Rago ETM Runs 1-12 Striped Bass - Latent (3), 488 (Box 12)
  - Scientific Studies, Box 13; 4
    Scientific Studies Large Paul Rago Runs-Z
    - Paul Rago Runs 13-24 White Perch - Direct & Indirect (1), 489 (Box 13)
    - Paul Rago Runs 13-24 White Perch - Direct & Indirect (2), 490 (Box 13)
    - Paul Rago Runs 13-24 White Perch - Latent (1), 491 (Box 13)
    - Paul Rago Runs 13-24 White Perch - Latent (2), 492 (Box 13)
    - Paul Rago Runs 25-36 Clureids - Direct & Indirect (1), 493 (Box 13)
    - Paul Rago Runs 25-36 Clureids - Direct & Indirect (2), 494 (Box 13)
    - Paul Rago Runs 25-36 Clureids - Latent Morality (1), 495 (Box 13)
    - Paul Rago Runs 24-36 Clureids - Latent Morality (2), 496 (Box 13)
    - No Title, 497 (Box 13)
- 5. Research Materials, 5; 1 linear foot 14 498 - 533
  Documents used by Hudson River Environmental Society for research.
  - Research Materials, Box 14; 5
    Documents used for research by HRES
    - 1972 and 1986 Environmental Quality Bond Acts, 498 (Box 14)
    - Analyzing NYS Streams for Possible Inclusion in the State Wile, Scenic, and Recreational River System, 499 (Box 14)
    - Annotated Code of Maryland - Water Resources Administration, 500 (Box 14)
    - Bibliography of Hudson Highlands, Hudson Valley, & Hudson River, 501 (Box 14)
    - Changes Between 1956 Zoning Ordinance and Proposed Zoning Ordinance - Poughkeepsie, 502 (Box 14)
    - Common Names of Fishes Collected in the Hudson River, 503 (Box 14)
    - Congressional Record - Senate, 504 (Box 14)
    - Cultural Landscapes - Rural Historic Districts in the National Park System, 505 (Box 14)
    - Dept. of Fish and Game Chapter III - Striped Bass, 506 (Box 14)
    - (the) Development Process in Westchester County - A Manual of Local, County, State, and Federal Permits, 507 (Box 14)
    - Drainage and Runoff - What Effects Does Development Have and How Can They Become Mitigated?, 508 (Box 14)
    - EAF Environmental Assessment Form, 509 (Box 14)
    - Environmentally Related Reports Since December 1974 (list), 510 (Box 14)
    - Feasibility and Design of Wet Ponds to Achieve Water Quality Control, 511 (Box 14)
    - Getting a DEC Permit, 512 (Box 14)
    - Greenway Act - Outline, 513 (Box 14)
    - Guidelines for Constructing Wetland Stormwater Basins, 514 (Box 14)
    - Guidelines for Soil Erosion and Sediment Control - CT, 515 (Box 14)
    - (a) Manual of Guidelines for New York’s River Program, 516 (Box 14)
    - Maryland Standard and Specifications for Soil Erosion and Sediment Control, 517 (Box 14)
    - Monitoring Guidance for the National Estuary Program 1992, 518 (Box 14)
    - New York Land Use, 519 (Box 14)
    - Results of Literature Search Concerning the Contribution of Hudson River Striped Bass to the Fisheries in Long Island Sound and the Atlantic, 520 (Box 14)
    - (the) Role of Easements in New York’s Open Space Planning, 521 (Box 14)
    - (the) Role of Technology and Engineering in Wetland Restoration and Creation, 522 (Box 14)
    - Scope for the Hudson River Natural Resource Damages Assessment Plan (draft), 523 (Box 14)
    - Sport Fishery Institute Bill 158, 524 (Box 14)
    - Standards and Specifications for Infiltration Practices - Maryland, 525 (Box 14)
    - Trends in Land Ownership, Greene County, 526 (Box 14)
    - U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service, 1969-1975, 527 (Box 14)
    - U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service, 1976-1978, 528 (Box 14)
    - U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service, 1979-1998, 529 (Box 14)
    - Westchester County Archaeology Resources Study, 530 (Box 14)
    - Work Plan for a Pilot Study on Predictive Modeling of Archeological Site Locations, 531 (Box 14)
    - Zoning Changes, 532 (Box 14)
    - Misc. Research Materials, 533 (Box 14)
- 6. Printed Materials, 6; 1 linear foot 15 534 - 633
  Pamphlets, brochures, newspaper and magazine clippings, reports, and publications relating to the Hudson River Environmental Society and the Hudson River Valley.
  - Reports and Proposals, 6.1
    - Reports and Proposals, Box 15; 6.1
      Reports and proposals concerning environmental issues in the Hudson River Valley
      - Abstracts for Conserving Biodiversity in River Habitats, 534 (Box 15)
      - Activity Report, 1977, 535 (Box 15)
      - Activity Report, 1978, 536 (Box 15)
      - Central Hudson Report 1995, 537 (Box 15)
      - Clean Lakes Program - A Review of the First Decade, 538 (Box 15)
      - Coastal Zone Management Book - Appendix II, 539 (Box 15)
      - Composite Annual Report 1980: New York, New Jersey, 540 (Box 15)
      - CPO-By-Objectives, 541 (Box 15)
      - ESF Quarterly, Spring 1993, 542 (Box 15)
      - Final List of Wild and Scenic Rivers, 543 (Box 15)
      - Financial Profiles of Five Marinas, 544 (Box 15)
      - Fishes of the Delaware Estuaries Errata and Additions, 545 (Box 15)
      - Greenway Conservancy Strategic Plan 1995-2005, 546 (Box 15)
      - Greenway Heritage Conservancy HRV, Inc., 547 (Box 15)
      - Greenway Update, Nov. 1989, 548 (Box 15)
      - Hudson River PCBs Superfund Site, July 1995, 549 (Box 15)
      - “Introduction” (no title), 550 (Box 15)
      - Maintaining Watercourses, 551 (Box 15)
      - Marina and Boatyard Financial Structure and Performance, 552 (Box 15)
      - Municipal Wastewater Treatment Works Construction Grants Program, 553 (Box 15)
      - News, 554 (Box 15)
      - NYS Legislative Commission on Rural Resources Annual Report 1988 (copy), 555 (Box 15)
      - NYS Legislative Commission on Rural Resources - List of Publications, etc., 556 (Box 15)
      - Plan for New York City - A Proposal, 557 (Box 15)
      - (the) Pollution Prevention Letter 1995, 558 (Box 15)
      - Proposal for Development of a Management Plan for Fish and Wildlife... Hudson River (Draft), 559 (Box 15)
      - Report on the Meeting of the Cornwall Fish Protection Board, Sept. 16-17, 1974, 560 (Box 15)
      - Sustainable Development, 561 (Box 15)
  - Newsletters and Publicationst, 6.2
    - Newsletters and Publications, Box 15; 6.2
      Newsletters and publications subscribed or of interest to HRES
      - Along the Walk, June 1992, 562 (Box 15)
      - (the) Amicus Journal, Summer 1993, 563 (Box 15)
      - Boating Industry 1985, 564 (Box 15)
      - Clearwater Navigator 1979, 565 (Box 15)
      - Clearwater Navigator 1980, 566 (Box 15)
      - Clearwater Navigator 1981, 567 (Box 15)
      - Clearwater Navigator 1982, 568 (Box 15)
      - Clearwater Navigator 1983, 569 (Box 15)
      - Clearwater Navigator 1984, 570 (Box 15)
      - Clearwater Navigator 1992, 571 (Box 15)
      - Dirty Dozen 1996, 572 (Box 15)
      - Econotes, 573 (Box 15)
      - EnviroNEWS, 574 (Box 15)
      - Environmental Action, Summer 1992, 575 (Box 15)
      - (the) Environmental Magazine, July/Aug 1992, 576 (Box 15)
      - Fishery Bulletin of the Fish and Wildlife Service, 577 (Box 15)
      - Friends of the Earth, Vol. 22 No. 1, 578 (Box 15)
      - Friends of the Earth, Vol. 22 No. 5, 579 (Box 15)
      - Friends of the Earth, Vol. 22 No. 6, 580 (Box 15)
      - (the) Grandeur of the Hudson, 581 (Box 15)
      - (the) Hudson River Trail, 582 (Box 15)
      - Hudson River Quarterly, 583 (Box 15)
      - Hudson Valley Insider’s Guide, 1990, 584 (Box 15)
      - Hudsonia 1994, 585 (Box 15)
      - Hudsonia Newsletter, 586 (Box 15)
      - (the) Index of Leading Cultural Indicators Vol. 1 1993, 587 (Box 15)
      - Inform for Action, 588 (Box 15)
      - Next Decade Program - Columbia County Conference, 589 (Box 15)
      - Next Decade Program - Greene County Conference, 590 (Box 15)
      - New York Environmental News, 591 (Box 15)
      - Pamphlets, 592 (Box 15)
      - Publications of the Hudson River Valley Commission 1967, 593 (Box 15)
      - Recent Publications from the Hudson River Monitoring Program (List), 594 (Box 15)
      - (the) Record, 595 (Box 15)
      - River: The Journal of the Hudson River Fishermen, 596 (Box 15)
      - River Voices, 597 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1974, 598 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1976, 599 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1980, 600 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1981, 601 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1982, 602 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1983, 603 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1984, 604 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1985, 605 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1986, 606 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1987, 607 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1988, 608 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1989, 609 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1990, 610 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1991, 611 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1992, 612 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News 1993, 613 (Box 15)
      - Scenic Hudson News Update 1987, 614 (Box 15)
      - Sea History 1985, 615 (Box 15)
      - Storage Characteristics of New York City’s Recreational Fleet, 616 (Box 15)
      - Suffolk County Agricultural News, No. 9, 617 (Box 15)
      - Tourism: An Industry with Promise for Sustainability, 618 (Box 15)
      - Trailblazer, Vol. 6 No. 4, 619 (Box 15)
      - Trailblazer, Vol. 18 No.6, 620 (Box 15)
      - Watershed, 621 (Box 15)
      - Water Ways, 622 (Box 15)
      - What’s in the Works, On the Boards, In Their Dreams, 623 (Box 15)
  - Maps, 6.3
    - Maps, Box 15; 6.3
      Various maps of the Hudson River Valley
      - Adirondack Park Open Space Protection Plan, 624 (Box 15)
      - Downtown Manhattan Office Building, 625 (Box 15)
      - Hudson Riverfront Design, 626 (Box 15)
      - Hudson River, New York to Wappingers Creek, 627 (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous, 628 (Box 15)
      - New York State Oil and Gas Fields (large), 629 (Box 15)
  - Clippings, 6.4
    - Clippings, Box 15; 6.4
      Newspaper and magazine clippings
      - Clippings, 1970s, 630 (Box 15)
      - Clippings, 1980s & 1990s, 631 (Box 15)
      - Clippings, Not Dated, 632 (Box 15)
      - Press Release, 633 (Box 15)
- 7. Legal Documents, 7; 3 linear feet 16 - 18 634 - 791
  Legal papers, such as testimonies, correspondence, stenographers’ reports, etc, related to cases worked on or in the interest of the Hudson River Environmental Society and the Hudson River Valley.
  By subject, alphabetically
  - Legal Papers, 7.1
    - Legal Papers, Box 16; 7.1
      Legal papers pertaining to environmental trials of the Hudson Valley
      - Affidavit: Clark, John, 634 (Box 16)
      - Affidavit: Goodyear, Dr. C. Phillip, 635 (Box 16)
      - Affidavit: Hall, Charles A. S., 636 (Box 16)
      - Affidavit: Raney, Dr. Edward C., 637 (Box 16)
      - Affidavit: Vandivert, Rod, 638 (Box 16)
      - Applicant’s Reply to the Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law..., 639 (Box 16)
      - Attachment 1, 640 (Box 16)
      - Attachment 2, 641 (Box 16)
      - Attachment 3, 642 (Box 16)
      - Brief - Alleged Violations of Sections 17-0501, 17-0511, and 11-1503... by GEC, 643 (Box 16)
      - Clarification of MCF-5 - Testimony and Exhibits, 644 (Box 16)
      - Covering Comments of Dr. Charles A. A. Hall, 645 (Box 16)
      - Errata to Exhibit 3, 646 (Box 16)
      - Evised Exhibits of Forrest R. Hauck Commission Staff Witness, 647 (Box 16)
      - Exhibit II: Comparison of Water Quality Classifications and Standards..., 648 (Box 16)
      - Exhibit 11: Attachment E, 649 (Box 16)
      - Exhibit 11: Attachment F, 650 (Box 16)
      - Exhibit 59, 651 (Box 16)
      - Exhibit 84-A, 652 (Box 16)
      - Exhibit CE-2: Parties Responsible for Exhibit CE-1, 653 (Box 16)
      - Exhibit: Fish Authority Board, 654 (Box 16)
      - Exhibit: Further Biological & Engineering Study Program …, 655 (Box 16)
      - Hearing Memorandum on Behalf of Utilities, 656 (Box 16)
      - Information Requests Directed to EPA Exhibits..., 657 (Box 16)
      - Interrogatories: 7 March 1973, 658 (Box 16)
      - Interrogatories: Austin, Garrett E., 659 (Box 16)
      - Interrogatories: Azzaro, Richard A., 660 (Box 16)
      - Interrogatories: Con Ed. Staff, 661 (Box 16)
      - Interrogatories: Federal Energy Regulatory Commission’s Staff, 662 (Box 16)
      - Interrogatories: Gluckstern, Henry, 663 (Box 16)
      - Legal Correspondence, 1974-1978, 664 (Box 16)
      - Legal Correspondence, 1979, 665 (Box 16)
      - Legal Correspondence, 1980, 666 (Box 16)
      - Legal Correspondence, Not Dated, 667 (Box 16)
      - Legislation, 668 (Box 16)
      - List of Exhibits Filed with EPA Region II, 669 (Box 16)
      - List of Exhibits on Storm King Proceedings (legal size), 670 (Box 16)
      - Motion to Amend Pre-Hearing Schedule and for Pre-Hearing Conference - Cornwall, 671 (Box 16)
      - Opinion Analyzing Plans Filed Pursuant to Section 149 of the Public Service Law and Order Directing Changes in Future Submissions, 672 (Box 16)
      - Opinion and Order Issuing License, 673 (Box 16)
      - Order Directing Prompt Completion of Hearings and Denying Without Prejudice Motion to Reopen in Full, 674 (Box 16)
      - Order Granting Motion for Deferral and Denying Motion to Vacate License, 675 (Box 16)
      - Order of Proof: Kinser, Dr. Glenn W., 676 (Box 16)
      - Order of Proof: Kinser, Dr. Glenn W. (duplicate), 677 (Box 16)
      - Order to Clerk 01/16/1980, 678 (Box 16)